(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T13:51:24.086595",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Once upon a time... in another world.
A girl was studying... at an academy of magic.
[A FEW YEARS LATER]
Who can show me a blue illumination spell?
Oh come on, you should all know this by now!
Pavolia Reine.
Yes!
Amazing work, Miss Reine!
Amazing, Reine!
Teach me!
How did you become so good, Reine?!
Oh, it's just a lot of studying!
Can you share us your routine?!
Sure!
Every day, I wake up at 5am.
I take a shower, do some exercises, and make a cup of tea!
Then I go through just 4 or 5 spellbook volumes before class.
Oh no...
That's kinda hard...
It's not that bad once you get used to it!
I bet you're gonna score perfectly on the potions exam today.
Potions exam?!
Oh no.
How could I forget?!
Ah. It's marked as pancake day.
Why did I remember pancake day and not the potion exam?!
I guess 4 hours of sleep is catching up to me...
Well! Whatever! I'll do my best!
I speed-read through all 6 alchemy and potion brewing books I had... I can do this!
And... you may all begin!
A bit of this... and a bit of that...
Wait...
Miss Reine, is your potion quite alright?
Yes, teacher! It should be... I added in unicorn hair, and a dash of cinnamon.
A dash of cinnamon?! No!! That's a portal potion, Reine!!
Wha-?! Did my memory get jumbled?!
Everyone, get to the back of the classroom!!
Why did I try to speed-read the entire compendium?!
NOOO!!!
REINE!!!
Noooo!!!!
Huh?
Where am I...?
What strange buildings...
I sense... magic...
Who're you?
...A zombie?
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonder,
Bentangkan sayap, ku melaju ke dunia baru
Spread your wings, I rush toward a new world.
Mentari tlah tiba
The sun has arrived,
Kini sudah saatnya
Now is the time at last,
Tantangan yang dinanti-nantikan
For the challenge we've all been awaiting.
Sang putri merak
The peacock princess,
Tertiup angin
Caught in the breeze,
Tak sengaja berpindah dunia
Accidentally drifted to another world.
Di tanah yang tak dikenal
In a land unknown,
Misteri berlalu-lalang
Mysteries passing by,
Kumpulkan tekad
Gather your resolve,
Gapai harapan
Seize your hopes,
Kan kurajut satu mimpi baru
I'll weave a brand new dream.
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonder,
Bentangkan sayap, magic 'kan kau saksikan
Spread your wings, and you shall witness magic.
Lebur duka, mari berdansa
Melt away sorrow, let's dance together,
Kutunjukkan
I will show you
Biru tak terlupakan
An unforgettable blue.
Kilau hanya untukmu
Its radiance is only for you.
Mentari tlah tiba
The sun has arrived,
Semangat yang membara
With a burning passion,
Di dunia yang silih berputar
In a world that keeps on spinning.
Sang putri merak
The peacock princess
Tak sabar menanti
Can't wait to see
Esok seperti apa yang tiba
What kind of tomorrow awaits us.
Di tanah yang tak dikenal
In this land unknown,
Setitik cahaya terang
A tiny spark of bright light—
Kuatkan hati, lekas berlari kabulkan mimpi
Strengthen your heart, run fast to grant your dreams!
Kan kurajut tanpa rasa ragu
I'll weave them without any doubt.
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonder,
Lukiskan warna dalam berjuta angan
Paint colors into millions of daydreams,
Suka cita tiada tara
With incomparable joy,
Kau saksikan, sinar biru menjulang
You witnessed a soaring blue light.
Genggam erat tanganku
Hold my hand tightly.
Hari-hari kulewati
I spent my days
Bersamamu di sini
Being here with you.
Tawa canda, suka duka kubagi
Laughter and jokes, joys and sorrows shared,
Dari rajutan mimpi, kini ku tak sendiri
From woven dreams, now I'm no longer alone.
Dengan dirimu slalu menerangi
With you always illuminating my way.
Bukalah gerbang keajaiban
Open the gates of wonder,
Permandangan yang tlah kau nanti-nantikan
The scenery you've been waiting for so long.
Lebur duka, mari berdansa
Melt away sorrow, let's dance together,
Kutunjukkan biru tak terlupakan
I will show you an unforgettable blue.
Kilau hadir untukmu
Its radiance is here for you.
あの青空のせいだ
It's all because of that blue sky.
キミの笑顔きらめく雨上がりの午後
Your smiling face sparkles on a post-rain afternoon.
絶妙な視線 痛いくらいに
Your exquisite gaze is almost painful,
ドキドキした いたずらに風が吹く
My heart raced as a playful wind blew.
めくれるページを隠したとたんに
The moment I hid the turning pages,
世界中がぐるぐる回る
The whole world started spinning around and around.
気づかれたくないな でも以上になれるかな
I don't want you to notice, but can I be more than this?
溢れそう 泣そう だめだよ
It's about to overflow, I might cry, no, I mustn't!
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky.
キミの笑顔きらめく雨上がりの午後
On the rainy afternoon when your smile sparkled,
絶妙な視線痛いぐらいどきどきした
Your exquisite gaze made my heart beat so fast.
いたずらに風が吹く 捲るページを隠した途端に
A mischievous wind blew, suddenly hiding the turning page.
世界中がぐるぐる回る
The whole world spins round and round.
気付かれたくないな
I don't want you to notice,
でも今以上になれるかな
But can I become more than this?
溢れそう泣きそうダメだよ
Overflowing, about to cry, no I can't!
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky.
キミも同じであれと願う
I wish you feel the same way too.
まぶしいshine 見えないふたりのline
A dazzling shine, an invisible line between us two,
手繰り寄せたなら would you be mine?
If I pull it closer, would you be mine?
妄想する物語も そうスルーするだけの恋のループ
Even fantasy stories are just looping love stories that get bypassed.
気付かれたくないな
I don't want you to notice,
でも今以上になりたいんだ
But I want to be more than this.
溢れそう泣きそうどうして
Overflowing, about to cry, why?
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky.
両手陽を遮って俯いた
Shielding the sun with both hands, I looked down.
この恋はどこまで？
How far will this love go?
終わらせたくない想い
Feelings I don't want to end.
打ち明ける勇気が出せる日まで
Until the day I find the courage to confess.
だんだん大きくなる影は
The shadow growing larger and larger
キミとふたりであれ
Is that I want to be with you, just the two of us.
夜になるとすぐに会いたくなるよ
When night falls, I immediately want to see you.
綺麗な星の光
The light of beautiful stars,
それより明日がいい
Tomorrow is even better than that.
ずっと隣にいさせてほしい
I want you to let me stay by your side forever.
あの青空のせいだ
It's because of that blue sky.
キミも同じであれと願う
I wish you feel the same way too.
この恋はどこまで？
How far will this love go?
終わらせたくない想い
Feelings I don't want to end.
打ち明ける勇気が出せる日まで
Until the day I find the courage to confess.
だんだん大きくなる影は
The shadow growing larger and larger
ちょっと待ってて
Please wait just a moment.
この恋はどこまで
How far will this love go?
打ち明ける勇気を
The courage to confess...
ラララララ
La la la la la...
Woah!
Whose 3D showcase is this? Whose 3D showcase is this?!
You guys are right!
Attention please! I'm Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2!
Tapi harian, sang putri merak yang tertiup angin, aku Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID Generasi 2!
Attention please! Hololive ID nixie! Pavolia Reine!
Welcome to Reine's very, very special tea party!
Oh, before we start, please do tweet with this hashtag, this hashtag #PavoliaReine3D!
My child, please tweet because I would like to hear your consoles and opinion about the live!
So, what are you waiting for? Tweet right now or later if you want!
ぜひぜひね、ツイートしてあげてください。ぜひぜひね、ツイート...あわすからんか！
Please tweet, everyone. Please, please... awaskalonga!
そう、そうですね。あの、最初から2曲、あの、2曲連続歌いましたね。あの、最初は Gate Open Start と、あの、あの青空のせいだ。
So, yeah. I started off with two songs, two songs in a row. First was "Gate Open Start" and "Ano Aozora no Sei da."
Both are Reine's original songs! Yay!
あ、待って。Oh no!
Ah, wait. Oh no!
What am I going to do? I got to clean! But before that,
let me show you guys,
show you guys this model!
How do you think I look?
No, you don't see anything.
Camera, camera, camera, camera, camera! Okay! Yes! Woo! You don't see—
Yeah! Nice, right? Oh, Reine's back! Oh my god, for real!
Reine, um, yeah! You don't see anything!
Who, except me, in my very clean room! Yay! Clean room!
Okay! Ah, but for real though, ah, what am I going to do?
The 3D showcase, the private tea party is today!
But my room is still a mess! Oh no,どうしようね！
But my room is still a mess! Oh no, what should I do?
今日はお披露目だったのに部屋はめちゃめちゃダティですね！
Today was supposed to be the reveal, but my room is so dirty!
No! I've got some guests coming too!
What do I do? What do I do?
I guess I got to get cleaning, huh?
Oh well
Ah... I don't want to do this, but
Wait, just wait a little bit, okay?
ちょっと待ってて ちょっと待ってて
Just wait. Just wait.
これからは掃除します それで よっ
From now on, I'm gonna clean. And so, yo...
Wait. Wait. Wait. It's...
Yeah
And this one, this one's like the heaviest. But it's okay.
We're putting this aside. So the camera, it won't be...
We're putting this aside. So the camera won't be...
I did a lot of cleaning, right? めっちゃ掃除... めっちゃ掃除した
I did a lot of cleaning, right? I cleaned so, so much.
And because, you know, I'm feeling a little bit thirsty, ne? 掃除終わったからね、喉が ちょっと ちょっとハウス 喉が乾いたんですね
And because, you know, I'm feeling a little bit thirsty. Since I finished cleaning, my throat... is a little dry.
So, now... I'm gonna drink a little bit. Let's drink.
ぅっと
Mmm...
Oh! しゅーえ あわさわさわさわさわさわさ... あ、ちょっとちょっと
Oh! Woo... Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa... Ah, wait, wait, wait!
いや、ごめんね。いや、いや、かもね。いや、いや、いや... I think, okay. Wah...
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, maybe, yeah... I think, okay. Whoa...
Yeah, okay. I think uh I think that was perfect. ばっちりですね
Yeah, okay. I think... I think that was perfect. Spot on.
Hi! Everybody, for you, welcome to Reine tea party! And, it's time to... come by, cheers! For the tea.
Hi! Everyone, this is for you. Welcome to Reine's tea party! And it's time to... come on, cheers for the tea!
グルグルグルグルグルグル... ぷーん、全部、あんじーる
*Slurp slurp slurp* It spilled everywhere, damn!
Okay. And now, uh, what's it called? because we already done with the tea, I'm now energized. We can clean more.
Okay. And now, um... what's it called? Because we're already done with the tea, I'm now energized! We can clean more.
Chin-chin-chin-chin-chin. これすきめえ It kills me. しゅーすーすーすー
Chin-chin-chin-chin-chin. It kills me. *Swish swish swish*
And it's time to clean! Let me get the broom.
Broom, broom, broom, broom, broom, broom, broom, broom. Tada!
I have the broom. ふっ Where is the gomii?
I have the broom. Whew, where is the trash?
Oh my god, okay. ふう
Oh my god, okay. Whew...
Go! じゅーじゅー
Go! *Swish swish*
や、や、や、や、や... Okay, okay. よ、まだ、まだ。よ、あ、よ。
Yeah, yeah, yeah... Okay, okay. Not yet, not yet. Here, ah, here.
Okay. Go! え、まだ？ Go! え... Go!
Okay. Go! Uh, not yet? Go! Uh... Go!
We got it! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
Dan kita buang the gomi.
And we throw away the trash.
That was so... tiring!
And then... But that's not done. Not yet because uh... I have a magic trick to show you. Tada!
And then... But that's not done. Not yet because... I have a magic trick to show you. Tada!
It's the はたき magic. It's the kamotet magic.
It's feather duster magic! It's the duster magic!
Ready to cleanse your soul? しゅーしゅーしゅーしゅーしゅー
Ready to cleanse your soul? *Swish swish swish swish swish*
Yes. Time to clean.
じゅんじゅんじゅん...
*Swish swish swish...*
Well, you know what? Look at this beautiful cityscape too. You guys like this place so much, right? But this is not all, you know?
Because I still have the bedroom to clean.
まだね、まだクリーニング、クリーニングがひつようヘアがあるから、lets... 掃除 the bedroom. Okay?
Still, since there's still cleaning needed here, let's... clean the bedroom, okay?
So, to the bedroom!
ぜんっ
Ta-da!
I am here! This is... This room might be familiar for you guys. Of course!
I am here! This... This room might be familiar to you guys. Of course!
And in here, we have the spicy, spicy, spicy, spicy brankas to upadar, and the head and... well, my my spare clothes spicy, so we can't show the contents of this one in this stream, okay?
And in here, we have the spicy, spicy, spicy safe... and my spare clothes, so we can't show the contents of this one in this stream, okay?
Gonna clean that, and there's uh... this too.
Gonna clean that. And there's, um... this too.
We got the fishing rod! Fishing rod... And we can clean this too. じゅんじゅん... まにまに、まにみみthings...
We got the fishing rod! Fishing rod... And we can clean this too. *Swish swish* Many, many things...
Punya. Disalah.
I have... Oh, my bad.
Fishing, fishing...
And then we go to this very, very special place...
...to chu-chu-chu my PC...
And oh, this is my... my desk mat with a specially drawn by Anemelfissa!
And oh, this is my... my desk mat specially drawn by Anemelfissa!
And Love Me Love Me also.
Look! It's Holoro desk mat, would you buy this? I think this is very nice, but too bad it's exclusive for me and me only for now.
Woo! Okay. Woo!
Okay, I think uh that's enough cleaning, right?
Let's just take a little break.
Ah, I'm satisfied.
And I think, no, it's time for someone to visit.
あの子も呼んじゃおっかな？
Shall I invite that girl too?
Say it with me! Three, two, one, ta-da!
Ta-da! Woo! Many, many tatang!
Tatang! Tatang! Oh!
Look at these tatangs! OMG!
Tatang! I've just cleaned this room!
さっきお掃除したばかりなのにね！
I just finished cleaning it!
Oh my god, well, let's pick up one, okay?
Many, many... Oops! Many, many tatang!
Yay! Hello! Tatang! Tatang! Tatang!
Tatang! Yay! Look at this! Tatang was lost, but he is here! He came to my 3D showcase!
OMG! こっちへ来いよ！ Wow! おっと、誰か落ちた。
OMG! Come over here! Wow! Whoops, someone dropped.
Many, many tatang falling, oh my god! So yeah, well...
Tatang! Please! Tatang, tatang! I want to um... I need to clean this room.
So here... um please tatang, I like it that you're... uh, I like it that you're falling down, but I need to soji, okay?
So here... um please tatang, I like it that you're... I like it that you're falling down, but I need to clean, okay?
So we can uh... we can move on to the guest segment, right? I've got a lot of special guests today actually. そうですね、ゲストパートに行きましょうか。
So we can uh... we can move on to the guest segment, right? I've got a lot of special guests today actually. Shall we go to the guest segment?
Yeah! Tatang! Tatang! Let's come back later! Syu-syu! Thank you! Thank you, tatang! We'll play again later!
ですね、今日はスペシャルゲストがたくさん来るよ。And uh where is the special guest, I wonder?
That's right, a lot of special guests are coming today! And uh where is the special guest, I wonder?
Mana ya? Tawannya? Oh!
Where could they be? I wonder? Oh!
Looks like somebody's already here! Oh, let's set the room up so we're ready for them, okay?
部屋も準備するね！ Yay! Change!
I'll get the room ready too! Yay! Change!
赤いたいようでドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress under the red sun,
私のこと見つめているの？
are you gazing at me?
目を逸らしたい　でも逸らせない
I want to look away, but I can't look away.
情熱で焼かれたい
I want to be scorched by passion.
トキメキ以上のリズム
A rhythm more than just excitement,
恋い知りたくて
I want to know love.
いつもより大胆な言葉をつぶやいた
I murmured words bolder than usual.
自分の気持ちなのに全然分からなく
Even though it's my own feelings, I don't understand them at all.
理性なんかじゃ制御不能
Reason is completely uncontrollable.
嫉妬に悶えて恋が届いてしまった
Writhing in jealousy, love has reached me.
恥ずかしく思うけどもっと知りたいの
I feel embarrassed, but I want to know more.
いけない夢だと気づきながら
Even while realizing it's a forbidden dream,
赤いたいようでドレスで踊る
dancing in a dress under the red sun,
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress of the red sun,
私のこと見つめているの？
are you gazing at me?
目をそらしたい でもそらせない
I want to look away, but I can't.
ああ情熱で焼かれたい
Ah, I want to be consumed by passion.
ときめき以上のリズム今宵知りたくて
Wanting to know a rhythm beyond excitement tonight,
いつもより大胆な言葉をつぶやいた
I whispered bolder words than usual.
自分の気持ちなのに全然わかんなくなっちゃいたいな
Even though they're my own feelings, I'm losing all grasp of them.
理性から指令が届かないコントロール不能
Commands from reason won't reach, uncontrollable.
そんな恋をしたいのって声が届いてしまった？
Did my voice saying I want that kind of love reach you?
恥ずかしいと思うけれどもっと知りたいのもっと知りたいの
I feel embarrassed, but I want to know more, I want to know more.
いけない夢だと気づかずに
Without realizing it's a forbidden dream.
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る 私のこと見つめているの？
Dancing in a dress of the red sun, are you gazing at me?
目をそらしたい でもそらせない 真夏の誰のモノ？
I want to look away, but I can't. Whose is midsummer?
あなたとわたしのものにしたい
I want to make it ours, yours and mine.
だってね心が止まらない季節に初めて胸の扉が開きそうよ You knock knock my heart!
Because in a season where my heart won't stop, the door to my chest is about to open for the first time. You knock knock my heart!
ためらいがちなステップが熱く変わる頃
As hesitant steps turn passionate,
いつもならありえない衝動にとまどうの
I'm bewildered by an impulse impossible normally.
あなたの手と私の手を重ねたら何か始まる？
If I place my hand on yours, what begins?
花火が照らす横顔
A profile illuminated by fireworks.
きっと思い出が来ると予感してた私 もう戻れない戻りたくない
I had a feeling this day would come; I can't go back, I don't want to go back.
真夏に誘われて あなたとわたしの夏にしたい
Enticed by midsummer, I want to make it our summer, yours and mine.
だってね心が止まらない季節 甘く切ない香りでふいに泣きたくなる気がしたの
Because in a season where my heart won't stop, a sweet, bittersweet scent suddenly made me want to cry.
近づいたり離れたりのダンスで頭狂ってるの
My head is going crazy with this dancing of getting close and pulling away.
ここにいてよ ここにいてよ もうこわくないの何もかもが
Stay here, stay here, nothing is scary anymore.
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る 私のこと見つめているの？
Dancing in a dress of the red sun, are you gazing at me?
目をそらしたい でもそらせない 真夏の誰のモノ？
I want to look away, but I can't. Whose is midsummer?
あなたとわたしのものにしたい
I want to make it ours, yours and mine.
だってね心が止まらない季節に初めて胸の扉が開きそうよ You knock knock my heart!
Because in a season where my heart won't stop, the door to my chest is about to open for the first time. You knock knock my heart!
ああ情熱的に抱きしめて！
Ah, embrace me passionately!
赤い太陽のドレスで踊る
Dancing in a dress of the red sun,
私のこと見つめている瞳
the eyes gazing at me,
目をそらしたい でもそらせない
I want to look away, but I can't.
真夏の誰のモノ？
Whose is midsummer?
あなたとわたしのものにしたい
I want to make it ours, yours and mine.
だってね心が止まらない季節 初めて胸の扉が開きそうよ You knock knock my heart!
Because in a season where my heart won't stop, the door to my chest is about to open for the first time. You knock knock my heart!
ああ情熱的に抱きしめて！
Ah, embrace me passionately!
And that was Manatsu wa Dare no Mono?
And that was "Whose is Midsummer?"
And my guest was Kiara-chan!
Kie-chan! Kiken-ki!
Hololive English no... chakanashi Kiara desu.
Hololive English's... Takanashi Kiara here.
I was invited to my little bird Kohai's showcase, which was so exciting.
Thank you for being such a... strict... strict...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. We had a... we had one, only one dance lesson together where there was no teacher.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. We had one, only one dance lesson together where there was no teacher.
So I took the position of the teacher, and when Reine was on the floor taking a break, I was like...
"Reine, get up! We have to dance! Get up, get up!"
"We have no time! We have to studio for two hours only!"
"We have no time! We only have the studio for two hours!"
I wanted to review the floor instead.
"The floor? Okay."
"It's very nice. Yeah, we can review this floor."
"What do you think about the sound?" "Well, I mean, it should be wood. Do we hear wood?"
"It doesn't seem to be wood, huh?"
"Wait, wait, Reine. We knocked knocked the floor." "We knocked knocked the floor!"
"It's mystery flooring, but it's 10 out of 10. Bird approved."
"I think to you every floor is 10 out of 10." "It is, as long as it's cool enough to lie down on."
"Oh my god, really quickly, we have to do some cute poses, okay?"
"I want to do this."
"Screenshot time! Use #ReineBirthday hashtag, it's somewhere up there." "Yeah, it's up there."
"And I want to do hug." "Ah, yes."
"And I want to do a hug." "Ah, yes."
"And let's do a shoot pose. Like secret agent, secret agent!"
So Reine, you still have some stuff to do, right?
Yes, thank you so much for coming! We were so happy to be able to dance with you!
Me too, let's do more soon!
Of course, yeah.
Bye-bye! Have fun!
And next song is Love Me Love Me.
And the next song is "Love Me Love Me."
ずっと 君の隣 じっと見てるばかり
Always by your side, just watching you intently,
相合傘止まない雨
Sharing an umbrella in the endless rain,
世界にふたりきり
Just the two of us in this world,
永遠刻むように 心臓 今この手に
As if carving eternity, holding our beating hearts in our hands right now,
どんな痛みさえも 愛のかたち
Even every pain is a shape of love.
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
Intertwining our pinkies bound by fate,
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
love me love me
ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ
I don't need myself, I don't need myself, I don't need myself.
キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ
I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you.
きゅっと抱きしめたら きっと逃げられない
If I hold you tight, you surely won't escape.
チクタク針が回る
Tick-tock, the clock hands spin,
世界にふたりきり
Just the two of us in this world,
現実壊すように 感情押し殺して
Crushing reality, suppressing our emotions,
どんな悲鳴さえも 愛のメロディ
Even every scream is a melody of love.
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
Intertwining our pinkies bound by fate,
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
love me love me
ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ
I don't need myself, I don't need myself, I don't need myself.
キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ
I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you.
愛して愛され 離れられない you and me ふたりきり でいい give me your love
Loved and loving, unable to part, you and me, just the two of us is fine, give me your love.
願うほど滴る赤い色
The red color dripping the more I wish,
何もかも染めてしまう愛をもっと頂戴
Give me more of that love that dyes everything!
もっと頂戴
Give me more!
ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ ワタシカイラナイ
I don't need myself, I don't need myself, I don't need myself, I don't need myself.
キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ キミガイラナイ
I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you, I don't need you.
love me love me
Wow! Hello everybody! Ah, right. I've got more people who want to celebrate with me today.
今日ですね、他にもお祝いしてくれた人たちが まだまだいるよー！
Today, you know, there are still more people who celebrated with us!
And they should be calling anytime soon. Kayak ada telepon gitu gak sih kayak...
And they should be calling anytime soon. Like, is there a phone call like...
Moshi-moshi? Hello? Can you hear me? Hello? Angkat, cepetan, lama.
Moshi-moshi? Hello? Can you hear me? Hello? Pick up, hurry up, so long.
Nah, gitu dong. Halo?
There you go. Hello?
Woi! Halo! Anjir suaranya kayak gitu.
Hey! Hello! Damn, what's with that voice?
Hello! Moshi-moshi? Oh ya, moshi-moshi, apa password-nya?
Hello! Moshi-moshi? Oh ya, moshi-moshi, what's the password?
Eh, "Marie White coffee, enak!" Woah! Cumaan! Rp200.000? Tapi bohong!
Uh, "Marie White coffee, is delicious!" Woah! Only! 200,000 rupiah? Just kidding!
Ayo bagi, Rp100.000, Rp100.000.
Let's split it, 100,000, 100,000.
Iya benar, bagi dua, biar adil. Oke, oke. Vesu and Kobo, thank you so much for coming! Makasih banget sudah datang ke acaranya Tanten Reine hari ini.
Yeah right, split in two, to be fair. Okay, okay. Vesu and Kobo, thank you so much for coming! Thank you so much for coming to Auntie Reine's event today.
Yoi! Asik! Aku mau ngucapin selamat dan apa nih? "3D" oh akhirnya!
Yeah! Awesome! I wanna say congratulations and what's this? "3D" oh finally!
Buset, ini Risu lagi, mana sih lu? Toilet? Diterawang aja.
Good grief, Risu is again, where are you? Toilet? Just clairvoyance.
Masih suaranya ditrawang aja ya.
You can just imagine our voices for now, ya.
Kalian kenalan dulu dong kepada para viewers.
Introduce yourselves first to the viewers.
Oh ya, halo tuh.
Oh yeah, say hello.
Halo! Aku oh oh oh definitely not in toilet,
Hello! I'm... definitely not in the toilet,
Ayunda Risu, Hololive Indonesia gen satu.
Ayunda Risu, Hololive Indonesia Gen 1.
Heh.
Yay!
Terus sebelahnya, aku BokuBokuBoku Boku wa Risu-at-your-service, Kohaku sayangan, Pavolia Reine, Putri Merak, Boku wa Reine desu.
And next to her, I'm... Risu-at-your-service, beloved amber, Pavolia Reine, the peacock princess, Boku wa Reine desu.
Asyik, asyik.
Nice, nice!
Yay, oke.
Yay, okay.
Gitu toh. Agak di sini aku mau meminta kalian untuk, request-request pose untuk screenshot time gitu nggak sih?
Like that. Here I want to ask you guys to, you know, request poses for screenshot time, right?
Apa aja boleh sebenarnya, bebas aja biar seru gitu loh.
Anything is fine actually, just anything to make it fun.
Kalau gitu, kalau gitu yang seiso dulu ya, seiso.
If that's the case, let's do the seiso ones first, seiso.
Aku tadi tuh ya, sengang, neter sengang, melihat pose Reine dari samping.
Earlier I was... amazed, utterly amazed, seeing Reine's pose from the side.
Aku mau, Reine pose menyamping pegang pinggang.
I want Reine to pose sideways holding her waist.
Gini maksudnya. Ah, ayieee!
Like this, you mean. Ah, ayieee!
Kameranya dari samping! Kameranya dari samping!
The camera from the side! The camera from the side!
Oh, seru sekali.
Oh, how interesting.
Oh, kayak gini.
Oh, like this.
Oh my god.
Aduh, encok. EncoK, encok, ini agak dikertekin, encok.
Ouch, my back aches. My back aches, let's crack it a bit, ouch!
Aku aku, yes yes yes what?
Me, me! Yes, yes, yes, what?
Oi, aku dulu apa risu dulu nih?
Oi, me first or Risu first?
Bebas, bebas, bebas.
Free, free, free!
Ya udah, ya udah.
Alright then, alright.
Enggak deh, Risu dulu deh, apa deh?
No, Risu first then, what should it be?
Ya udah ya udah.
Alright, alright.
Aku ya, aku ya. Eh tadi pose di samping, tapi tangan satunya tuh nunjuk ke bibir. Ngerti nggak?
Me, ya, me, ya. Earlier, pose sideways, but one hand is pointing at the lips. Get it?
Gimana sih?
How is that?
Pegang pinggang, pegang pinggang.
Hold the waist, hold the waist.
Tangannya agak korset nih.
Her hands are a bit corseted here.
Tangan kirinya tuh kayak shut shut shut, diam diam gitu.
Her left hand is like, shut shut shut, quiet, quiet like that.
Ah ya gitu deh pokoknya, ya agak sebisanya ya guys. Ata- taha- bisa gini.
Ah yeah, just like that, do your best, guys. Ah- taha- can do it like this.
Iya siap, siap, siap.
Yes, ready, ready, ready!
Wah, bange-!
Wow, so ba-!
Okelah, bolehlah, bolehlah. Aku yang pilih sekarang nih.
Okay then, alright, alright. I'll choose now.
Boleh, boleh.
Sure, sure.
Apa? Pargoy sekarang.
What? Pargoy now.
Pargoy? Pargoy itu kayak apa ya? Pargoy itu kayak apa?
Pargoy? What's pargoy like? What is pargoy?
Nggak tahu deh, sedapat lu aja dah.
I don't know, just however you can get it.
Ya. Itu, boset, goyang ngebor ya.
Yeah. That, boset, drilling dance, ya!
Tante, jangan tante. Generation gap, generation gap!
Auntie, don't, auntie! Generation gap, generation gap!
Bisa ya goyang ngebor.
You can do the drilling dance!
Tante, jangan, jangan ngebor. Yes!
Auntie, don't, don't drill! Yes!
Habis itu, bos apa lagi nih?
After that, what boss/pose next?
Terakhir, yang lain ya, sebentar-sebentar ni, ini gini.
Last one, others ya, wait-wait, this is like this.
Lu, lu ini, Tante.
You, you this, Auntie.
Pose lari mau entry ke side A.
Running pose wanting to entry into Side A.
Oh ya, oke oke. Gua bisa banget tuh. Pake faundo, pake faundo.
Oh yeah, okay okay. I can totally do that. Use faundo, use faundo.
Enemy sighted! Enemy sighted!
Headshot!
Tidak, tidak, tidak. Cek corner soalnya ya.
No, no, no. Checking corners, you see, ya.
Makasih ya, udah-udah.
Thank you, already, already.
Aku senang banget pinjam kolam renangnya ya, bye-bye.
I'm so happy to borrow the swimming pool, ya, bye-bye!
Hah? Bye-bye.
Huh? Bye-bye!
Ya udah sih, paling nanti dicegat satpam. Thank you Kobo and Risu from Hololive Indonesia for memeriahkan my tea party!
Oh well, maybe she'll get intercepted by security guards later. Thank you Kobo and Risu from Hololive Indonesia for enlivening my tea party!
Well, it looks like we got even more guests. Who do you think is gonna show up next? There, my senpais.
Japanese mode. Moshi-moshi? Kikoemasu ka?
Japanese mode. Moshi-moshi? Can you hear me?
Wah!
Halo!
Hello!
Congratulations! Congratulations! Omedetou senpai, subaru senpai.
来てくれてありがとう。今日はえっとEnglish、今日はEnglish？
Thank you for coming. Today is, um, English? Today is English?
Japanese language? Today is English or Japanese?
Um, English or Japanese?
Um, English or Japanese? Ah, Japanese only, yes?
Yes, Japanese only! Ano, onegaishimasu, please. Japanese only, Towa senpai and Subaru senpai, desu ne. Yay!
Onegaishimasu, yoroshiku onegaishimasu! Ne, ano konkai wa desu ne, chotto screenshot taimu no tame ni, ano request uketemasu yo. Ano, yes, donda pose ga hoshii ka.
Onegaishimasu, yoroshiku onegaishimasu! You see, this time, you know, for screenshot time, we're accepting requests. You know, yes, what kind of pose you want.
Ah demo, mazu ne, chotto dake, magic. Chotto magic.
Ah, but first, just a little bit, magic. Just a little magic.
Maji?
Seriously?
Chotto dake?
Just a little bit?
Wah!
Whoa!
Nani? Nani? Cleaning hatake desu.
What? What? It's a cleaning duster.
Cleaning hatake? Cleaning hatake?
Cleaning duster? Cleaning duster?
Sono cleaning hatake de, nanka pose request toka arimasu ka? Sono hatake de pose? Muzukute, sugee muzukashii n desu kedo.
With that cleaning duster, are there any pose requests? A pose with that duster? It's difficult, it's super difficult though!
なんですか？何ですか？
What is it? What is it?
えっと、えっと、まばゆいポーズでハタキで掃除しながら、Please say あらあら、Please。
Umm... with a dazzling pose, while cleaning with a duster, please say ara ara, please.
ああ、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
あ、違うわ、ごめん。
Ah, that's wrong, sorry.
あの… Cleaning… あ、あら、あら、It's time to 掃除！
Um... cleaning... ah, ara, ara, it's time to clean!
Yeah! Thank you, じゅにょれいね！ You are number one, じゅにょ！ Yeah!
Yeah! Thank you, Junyoreine! You are number one, Junyo! Yeah!
え、ほかのポーズありますか？じゃあ、次は…あのスバルちゃんを働いてどっかやってほしいです。
Eh, are there other poses? Well, next... I want Subaru-chan to work somewhere.
なんでそんなことあるんですか？
Why would you say something like that?!
なんで？スバルクリーニングでプリーズ！あ、スバルスバルクリーニング！オッケー。
Why? Subaru Cleaning, please! Ah, Subaru Subaru Cleaning! Okay.
Wait, we are bad friends!
オッケーオッケーオッケー。Is is good? Cleaning is good, right?
Okay, okay, okay. Is it good? Cleaning is good, right?
オッケー、サンキュー！オッケー！
Okay, thank you! Okay!
え、待って、ちょっとあのハタキで可愛いポーズしてみて。
Eh, wait, try doing a cute pose with the duster.
え、可愛いポーズ？ハタキと一緒に可愛いポーズ？めっちゃ難しそう。
Eh, a cute pose? A cute pose with the duster? That sounds super hard.
むずいよ。むずいよ。
It's hard. It's hard.
これ、これ、これ可愛い。キュートポーズ。
This, this, this is cute. Cute pose.
いや、いいのよ。いいのやって。お、待て、待て。
No, it's fine. Do it. Oh, wait, wait.
いや、ちょっともうそのあのボディがすごい。ナイスボディ過ぎるわ。
No, wait, that... um, your body is amazing. Too much of a nice body.
いや、ボディしか見てないやん！
No, you're only looking at the body!
ごめん、なんかうちなるおじさんでてる、ごめん。
Sorry, my inner old man is coming out, sorry.
やばいそこ、あ、やばい、やばいすぎる！
Oh no, that's... ah, oh no, way too dangerous!
え、じゃあどうすればいいんですか？背中みたいな。
Eh, then what should I do? Like your back?
背中？うわ…！ You are クリーニング say あらあら！
Back? Whoa...! You are cleaning, say ara ara!
プリーズ、せい、あらあら！あ、あら、あら、あら、あら、
Please say ara ara! Ah, ara, ara, ara, ara,
You are number one lady! Thank you! オッケー！
You are number one lady! Thank you! Okay!
オッケーですか？ Thank you so much! え、ありがとうございます！
Is that okay? Thank you so much! Eh, thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！いや、嬉しい！
Thank you very much! Yay, I'm so happy!
今度ね、なんかやりましょうね、一緒にね。やろう、やろう！
Next time, let's do something together, okay? Let's do it, let's do it!
よかったね、れいね！おめでとう！やったね、おめでとう！またね、ありがとう！バイバイ！
That's great, Reine! Congrats! Yay, congrats! See you, thanks! Bye-bye!
イエイ！そして That was Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai from Hololive JP!
Yay! And that was Towa-senpai and Subaru-senpai from Hololive JP!
I'm so happy! Many, many people coming. えー、ま、And then, some girls from the EN branch are also here!
I'm so happy! Many, many people coming. Eh, well, and then some girls from the EN branch are also here!
イアンからも来てくれましたね！回しましょう！ハロー！
Ina also came! Let's spin! Hello!
イエイ！ハロー！イエイ！ウォ、ウォ、ウォ、ウォ！あ、ちょっと、I need to hide this. 嘘、嘘、嘘！
Yay! Hello! Yay! Woah, woah, woah, woah! Ah, wait, I need to hide this. No, no, no!
Look at that! Looking good! Yeah, show this somewhere, secret! Secret, secret, secret, ハタキ Magic!
Look at that! Looking good! Yeah, show this somewhere, secret! Secret, secret, secret, duster magic!
オッケー！Whatever that you want to call it! Yay! Please introduce yourself, Gura, Calli, and IRyS!
Okay! Whatever you want to call it! Yay! Please introduce yourself, Gura, Calli, and IRyS!
ドウモ、サメデスウ。I'm Gawr Gura from Hololive English. Yay! Yay!
Domo, I'm shark. I'm Gawr Gura from Hololive English. Yay! Yay!
I'm Mori. Calli! I'm Mori Calliope from Hololive English. Yeah, let's go! Who's next?
And I'm IRyS. IRyS, it's IRyS. Hey. Hi. Thank you so much for coming today.
And so what we're going to do is I'm accepting requests from you for, you know, your screenshot time. I'll do any pose for you. Anything! Anything! Anything!
Alright, I'll go first. I'll go ahead and make it easy. Rip the band-aid off. Show us your panties!
Just do it. Just what?
Kids want what they want to see. Ah! Let's see. No, hear me out.
That's why I was thinking kicky—(Calli, is that what you were always thinking?) No, I'm just thinking about the fans!
I saw some— Oh, what, what, what? What just happened? Ah, I didn't. I didn't. What? Ah?
I've seen that magic. Suddenly I don't remember anything. Spaghetti people.
Anyways, what's next? I want to see a close-up of your ribs! My, this... This rib is ripped.
And walkie-talkie at the same time. It's a double tap. That should not be allowed. Oh my god!
Gura, how do you not have those? Are those like gills?
How do you not have those? No! What the hell? Those are like gills!
Any more requests? I got something to show you, too, actually after this.
Oh, it's a surprise.
I want to see you do a bridge.
A bridge?
Yeah.
A bridge kayak yang desuka? Kayak yang memang mengerti?
You have to lie down first, it's dangerous. How limber, blessed.
I don't know.
Ugh, I don't know how to... cameraman, cameraman.
No, oh no. Cameraman was not really cute in on the memo there.
Damn it!
No, no more re-broadcast, sorry, sorry.
We'll get him next time.
I got to show you something. Do you know who this is?
Show us, show us.
Oh, Mr. Tata! Tambourine!
Yeah, big old tata, looks like a post office.
My beloved.
My beloved Tatang, and I want to say a little bit of something.
This Tatang can grow big. You know, Tatang is small, right?
Like your chest?
Huh? What? Huh? No, no, no. Renish Tatas are not small.
Yeah, so like if you feel like um wait, wait, I'm just going to demonstrate it to you.
What're not?
No, they're not. I mean, just in case they get bigger.
Oh, bro, Tatang's going to get with tea! Oh, no!
With this tea, something, you can give more drink.
It's like a sponge and he's peeing it out right away! It's going right through him!
It's big Tatang! You got Tatang!
So, if you guys feel like you want to maybe, for example, grow bigger and stronger, like have a bigger heart or something,
So, if you guys feel like you want to maybe grow bigger and stronger, like have a bigger heart or something,
Yeah, you guys can call me and order this tea for me. Everybody join the royalty!
So, you know, if the tofu has a little problem or something,
I don't specifically need anything like that, but yeah.
I'm just saying, I'm not mentioning any names.
But maybe we can go bigger everywhere, everywhere.
Of course, if you take a bath with it, girl.
If you take a bath with it, then maybe like, you know, every single day, then maybe, but that's going to take a lot of tea.
If you take a bath with it every single day, then maybe, but that's going to take a lot of tea.
Sounds still like my mom telling me to drink milk every day of my childhood life.
Exactly, it's better.
Again. Oops, where do I put this?
Yeah, so um just call me guys if you need that, yeah.
Anyways, um that was great. I was so happy that so many people came to see me.
But I'm not done singing yet. There's still more.
So, mada otatai tarainai kara, I'm going to sing some place else maybe.
I want to sing in a place where I can sing as much as I like.
And then, so let's eat out!
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(DISCO LADY DISCO LADY DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう はじける BEAUTY LADY
Sweetie darlin', let's dance, the bursting beauty lady
生まれ変わって甘い夢 そっと彩りたいの
Reborn into a sweet dream, I want to softly color it
グラマラスなくちびる ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Glamorous lips, pink-colored glossy nails
ガラスの向こう側面に映る素顔 シュールなDays
The true face reflected on the other side of the glass, surreal days
キミだけにSO 見せていたい 心の中瞳の奥
I want to show only to you, deep within my eyes
AH 傍にいて欲しいの 月のMIRROR BALL 照らされて
Ah, I want you to be near me, illuminated by the moon's mirror ball
MY DARLIN' ねぇ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう はじける SEXY BEAUTY
My darlin', hey, let's have a vivid love, bursting sexy beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢 そっと彩るMY LOVE ほら 世界は変わる
Reborn into a sweet dream, softly coloring my love, see, the world changes
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
ドラマティックな情熱 褪せない デジャヴ 見続けたくて
Wanting to keep watching dramatic passion, fadeless déjà vu
カラフルなSWEETY STORY 心深く 刻み込む
A colorful sweety story engraved deep in my heart
小さな闇が 訪れても 恋の呪文 唱えたなら
Even if a small darkness visits, if I chant the spell of love
そう、きっと 果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが 降り注ぐ
Yes, surely the endless sky, a shower of stardust rains down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう 50/50あわせて
That's why let's aim for the happy station, matching 50/50
チュルチュルチュルパヤパ
(Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa)
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream,
そっと彩りたいの
I want to softly color it.
ほら
See,
世界は変わる
The world changes.
チュルチュルチュルパヤパ
Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa
ドラマティックな情熱 褪せないデジャヴ
Dramatic passion, unfading deja vu,
見続けたくて
I want to keep seeing it.
カラフルなスウィーティストーリー 心深く 刻み込む
A colorful sweety story, engraved deep in my heart.
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits,
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the spell of love,
そう、きっと 果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが 降り注ぐ
Yes, surely, a shower of stardust rains down.
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
That's why let's head towards HAPPY STATION.
50/50あわせて 100%以上の愛
Combining 50/50, over 100% love,
揺るぎなくここにあると 私思ってる
I believe it is firmly here without wavering.
プログレッシブと コンサバティブな自分
My progressive and conservative self,
キミにありのままを 好きでいて欲しい…と
I want you to love me just as I am...
願いが 叶うなら そうきっと
If my wish comes true, yes, surely
果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが 降り注ぐ
A shower of stardust rains down.
私を守ってよ
Protect me.
チュルチュルチュルパヤパ
Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa
ドラマティックな情熱 褪せないデジャヴ
Dramatic passion, unfading deja vu,
見続けたくて
I want to keep seeing it.
カラフルなスウィーティストーリー 心深く 刻み込む
A colorful sweety story, engraved deep in my heart.
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits,
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the spell of love,
そう、きっと 果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが 降り注ぐ
Yes, surely, a shower of stardust rains down.
プログレッシブと コンサバティブな自分
My progressive and conservative self,
キミにありのままを 好きでいて欲しい…と
I want you to love me just as I am...
願いが 叶うなら そうきっと
If my wish comes true, yes, surely
ふたりもっと 一緒に踊りましょう
Let's dance together even more,
SECRET NIGHT 素敵な ラブソングのデコレーション
SECRET NIGHT, the decoration of a wonderful love song,
2人のハートで AH 奏で合わせて
Playing together with our two hearts.
MY DARLIN' ねぇ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My darlin' hey, let's fall in a vivid love,
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting sexy beauty,
生まれ変わって甘い夢 そっと彩るMY LOVE
Reborn into a sweet dream, softly coloring my love,
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting sexy beauty,
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream,
そっと彩るMY LOVE ほら 世界は変わる
Softly coloring my love, see, the world changes.
チュルチュルチュルパヤパ
Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa
Oh my god! 愛のネタバレ「別れ」っぴいな
Oh my god! Spoiler warning, love's a bitch.
人生のネタバレ「死ぬ」っぴいな
Then someday, you'll close your eyes and never wake up.
なにそれ意味深で かっこいいじゃん...
Pardon me for getting deep, but isn't it cool?
それっぽい単語集で 踊ってんだ 失敬
This playbook of -isms got me dancing mad, my bad!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅ る ふ
Tu-tu-ru-tu-tu-tu-ru-fu
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Like that, I'm not.
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅ る ふ
Tu-tu-ru-tu-tu-tu-ru-fu
神っぽいな
Like a fucking god.
もういいぜ もういいぜ それも
That's enough, I'm fed up.
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたな
Didn't I tell you that's enough? But now I'm hyped up.
おっきいね おっきいね 夢
Dreaming big? Keep dreaming.
おっきいね おっきいね
Maybe your dream's the next big thing.
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
Profit's sweet, but a kind heart will spell the end.
うええい うええい
Gott ist tot.
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
Well aren't you blessed? Unlike the rest.
神っぽいな それ "My God"
Just like a fucking god ("My god").
アイウォンチュ ウォンチュ IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, my IQ drops.
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
A wicked witch, that's what you're like.
邪心っぽいな それ "My God"
That's all you'll ever be ("My god").
アイハイチュ ハイチュ 害虫はどっち
I hate you, hey who's the pest now, you or me?
その髪型 その目 その口元
It's your hair, your eyes, your lips,
その香水 その服 そのメイク
Your perfume, clothes, and makeup.
アレっぽいな それ 比況
Like that, I can't compare.
アレっぽいな それ
Like that, that's a match.
その名言 その意見 その批評
Wanna hear your hot takes, give us your review.
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
Do my bidding? Only kidding! Everybody flocks to you.
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
You're fucking godlike, unlike me.
ぽいな ぽいな ぽい 憧れちゃう!
Like this, like that, I want what you have!
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」ってぽいな
Spoiler for love: “break-up”-ish
人性のネタバレ 「死ぬ」ってぽいな
Spoiler for life: “death”-ish
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん…
That’s so meaningful and cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ 失礼
I’m dancing with a “-ish” word book, excuse me
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
That’s “-ish”, that’s “-ish”
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu
神っぽいな
That’s god-ish
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That’s enough, that’s enough
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなあ
That’s enough, I’m getting excited on the contrary
おっけいいね おっけいいね 夢
It’s big, it’s big, your dream
おっけいいね おっけいいね
It’s big, it’s big
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
Profitable, yet graciousness is the end
うええい うええい
Yaaay yaaay
“ Gott ist tot ”
“Gott ist tot”
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
That’s god-ish, unfair
神っぽいな それ “My God”
That’s god-ish, “My God”
アイウオンチュウ オンチュウ IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, my IQ's going down
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
That’s evil-hearted, ultimately
邪心っぽいな それ “My God”
That’s evil-hearted, “My God”
アイヘイチュウ ヘイチュウ 害虫はどっち
I hate you, hate you, who’s the pest now?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hair, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレっぽいな それ 比況
It’s “that”-ish, compare it’s “that”-ish
アレっぽいな それ
It’s “that”-ish
その名言 その意見 その批評
That quote, that opinion, that review
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, that gag, that taste
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
That’s god-ish, unfair
ぽいな ぽいな ぽい どこかれちゃうわ!
How “-ish”, “-ish”, “-ish” I’m so jealous!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
That’s “-ish”, that’s “-ish”
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
That’s “-ish”, that’s “-ish”
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
That’s “-ish”, that’s “-ish”
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる ふ
Tu tu-lu tu tu tu tu
神っぽいな
That’s god-ish
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」ってぽいな
Spoiler for love: “break-up”-ish
人性のネタバレ 「死ぬ」ってぽいな
Spoiler for life: “death”-ish
すべて理解してわづらった
I understood everything and suffered
無邪気に踊っていたかった人生
I just wanted to dance without knowing life
まりーん先輩ありがとうございました！
Marine-senpai, thank you very much!
ねえ、おめでとう！
Hey, congratulations!
お披露目呼んでくれてありがとね！
Thanks for inviting me to your showcase!
一緒に歌えて楽しかったよ！
It was so fun singing together!
まりーん先輩大好きです！
Marine-senpai, I love you so much!
まりんも大好きだよ！
Reine, I love you too!
またね、がんばってね、バイバイ！
See you later, do your best, bye-bye!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
はあ、嬉しいな
Ah, I'm so happy.
え、それじゃあそろそろラストの曲なんですが
Well then, it's almost time for the final song, but...
その前に、宣伝です！
Before that, a commercial!
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
[Title: Pavolia Reine Membership Promotional Video "The Royaltea"]
Attention please! Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKYats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights, which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties, which also means membership-exclusive streams in which we can have various talks, play games together, and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask? Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is... SAFETY IS GUARANTEED
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Kiss me！ 不思議つかないで
Kiss me, keep those lips from wandering off
Tell me 甘い言葉で
Tell me every sweet and tender thought
Give me 君のすべてを
Give me all you have to give and more...
今 この現実で
Fantasy's where futures are born!
このまま繋がる時間
Can you feel the beat? The rhythm, the tune...
油断しないでね
Your heart and mine - the countdown...
声を枯らすくらい
If you feel something coming to you,
心臓裂け叫べ
Believe it and scream it aloud!
今更恋しいなんて思わない
I don't think "I'll miss you..." anymore, like I did the day you left.
代わりはいくらでも眠るわ
There's so many just like you, I could use instead!
熱く燃える笑いをとおして
'Cause passion burning bright only hurts you in the end.
騒がし街へ まだ夜が明けて
This city will swallow the pain... / Tomorrow's another today...
まだまだ笑えない SHOWTIME
Curtain call's at dawn, darling! Showtime!
ほら踊り明かそうよ
Spend our moment dancing in the moonlight!
暗くらしちゃうくらいに見つめてね
'Til your gaze starts swaying with my body... / Keep your eyes on me!
TAKE ME 深い夜まで
Take me somewhere, deep into the night...
TOUCH ME 昨日向くままに
Touch me - here, there, anywhere you like!
TRUST ME 夢へ誘う
Trust me! Won't you let me look inside?
飽きるまでずっと
Fantasies and futures collide...
キスして 秘密を教えてよ
Kiss me... Tell me your secrets.
全てを預けて…
Give me everything...
強く生き続けることを誓うよ
I swear I'll keep on living strong.
優しいわたしはいないわ
The gentle me is no longer here.
さよならは必要ないから 叶わないでね
Goodbyes aren't necessary, so don't let it happen.
いつか終わるから
Because it will end someday.
正直な気持ちで 私を求めて
With honest feelings, desire me.
私を求めて 今すぐにしないで
Desire me, don't do it right now.
他に要らないでしょ 心繋がる場所で
You don't need anyone else, right? In the place where our hearts connect.
強く感じてよ 声を枯らしてでも
Feel it strongly, even if my voice goes hoarse.
心臓で叫べ 言わされた恋心なんて思わない
Scream from the heart. Don't think of it as manufactured romantic love.
愛してなんて言わないわ
I won't say "love me."
わりは誰も見えないから
Because I can't see anyone else taking your place.
熱く燃えるものを通して
Through that burning passion,
騒がしい夜の中 二人だけの世界で踊ろう
In the noisy night, let's dance in a world just for the two of us.
邪魔するものはないわ
There's nothing to get in our way.
さよならは言えないからね
I can't say goodbye, so...
心地いい夢へ続くイリュージョンナイト
To a pleasant dream, an illusion night continues.
まだまだ終わらないショウタイム
The showtime isn't over yet.
ほら踊り明かそうよ
Come on, let's dance the night away.
暗くらしちゃうくらいにはじけてね
So let loose until it's pitch dark.
邪魔するものはないわ
There's nothing to get in our way.
さよならは言えないからね
I can't say goodbye, so...
心地いい夢へ続くイリュージョンナイト
To a pleasant dream, an illusion night continues.
まだまだ終わらないショウタイム
The showtime isn't over yet.
ほら踊り明かそうよ
Come on, let's dance the night away.
暗くらしちゃうくらいにはじけてね
So let loose until it's pitch dark.
おおー！Thank you so much for today, everybody!
Whoa! Thank you so much for today, everybody!
みんな今日は本当にありがとう！
Thank you all so much for today!
そう、 yeah, that was Illusion Night!
That's right, yeah, that was Illusion Night!
And how did you like the collab as well? The duo! Nice!
And before I end things, I have an announcement.
そうですね、え、最後はAnnouncementがありますね！グッズ！グッズがあります！
That's right, um, lastly, there's an announcement! Goods! There are goods!
え、まずは、こちらですね！
Um, first of all, it's right here!
イェーイ！ おお！
Yay! Whoa!
Oh my god! Sweet Tonjok Hoodie!
Sweet Tonjok Hoodie, a hoodie just for you.
Well, look at that! The front part, the front part, there's an illustration by よまざか先生.
Well, look at that! The front part, there's an illustration by Yoma Saka-sensei.
And look at the sides! Look at this, sleeve design has Salam Merakyats! Perfect for the Merakyats who want to have a Tonjok identity! Phew phew phew phew phew phew phew!
The size of the hoodie is one-size-fits-all, so you don't have to worry about size, and the material is cotton! Yummy yummy! あ、and...
The size of the hoodie is one-size-fits-all, so you don't have to worry about size, and the material is cotton! Yummy yummy! Ah, and...
The goods will not be on sale immediately, it will be on sale in the holoro 3D collaboration on July 29.
The goods will not be on sale immediately. They will be on sale in the Hololive 3D collaboration on July 29.
グッズは、え、7月29日に sale始まります！イェー！楽しみにしててね！
The goods go on sale on July 29! Yay! Please look forward to it!
And I also have a very big announcement to share.
そ、え、大切な知らせがあります。んで、Take a look!
That's right, um, I have an important announcement. And then, take a look!
PAVOLIA REINE NEW ORIGINAL SONG
Produced by MARDIAL
Pavolia Reine's first ENGLISH x INDONESIAN COMING SOON
はーい！そう皆さん楽しみにしててね！
Hii! So everyone, please look forward to it!
And don't forget to tweet with the hashtag #PavoliaReine3D gokansol waiting waitingしますね！ Please tweet with hashtag ini!
And don't forget to tweet with the hashtag #PavoliaReine3D! Gokansol, I'm waiting, waiting! Please tweet with this hashtag!
And so, we reached the end of the night. Thank you so much everybody for watching Pavolia Reine's 3D showcase! みなさん本当にありがとね！
And so, we reached the end of the night. Thank you so much everybody for watching Pavolia Reine's 3D showcase! Thank you all so much!
それじゃあ、we say Salam Merakyats! バイバーイ！イェーイ！
Well then, we say Salam Merakyats! Bye-bye! Yay!
After waiting for so long, the time to celebrate and cheer has finally come! There are still so many things to see and experience in the story of Pavolia Reine, and I am forever grateful to have you all be part of it. I will always treasure the memories we have, and I'm excited to make new ones!
After waiting for so long, the time to celebrate and cheer has finally come!
There are still so many things to see and experience in the Story of Pavolia Reine,
and I am forever grateful to have you all be part of it.
I will always treasure the memories we have, and I'm excited to make new ones!
3D SHOWCASE